HUGO SIMÕES

hugosimoescontato@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hugosimoess/ https://github.com/hugosimoesdev

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A Computer Science graduate committed to excellence, I have been actively involved in crafting innovative digital solutions across various platforms since 2020. My passion for technology keeps me consistently abreast of the latest market trends.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Founder & Full Stack Developer

At Digisol June 2023 - Present

Digisol is a digital solutions startup that seamlessly integrates forward-thinking design with cutting-edge technology, creating narratives that not only transform but also elevate the brands of our partners.

- I have been engaged in the roles of Project Manager and Full Stack Web Developer.
- Developing websites using ReactJS and Wordpress. Always concerned with the User Experience and using Google Analytics.

Internship

At Cargill April 2020 - April 2021

Cargill provides financial and risk management solutions to clients in the agricultural, food, financial and energy sectors around the world.

- Intern as a developer in the Trade & Structured Finance sector. I used Java and Microsoft SQL Server for graphical interfaces, database queries and creating documentation.
- I had the opportunity to work with international teams such as England, Mexico, India and the United States.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

IFSP (Instituto Federal de São Paulo) February 2020 - December 2023

HARD SKILLS

- Web Development using ReactJS, NextJS, TailwindCSS, MongoDB, NodeJS and CMS platforms.
- 1 year professional experience with Java and Microsoft SQL Server.
- Other programming languages: VBScript, .NET, C#, C/C++, Python, etc.
- Familiarity with software architecture and design.
- Strong knowledge of Algorithms, Data Structure and Object Orientation.
- Experience with agile methods.
- Advanced English and basic Spanish.